Angel's Playbox Entrance
Recommended Level: 50
Loading
Begin Adventure
Episode 7\h\h\hGolden Raana Farming
Croak
Tremble
Scratch
Attack: 67
Defense: 200
15% Defense Penetration
Monster: Toy Box
exhale
inhale
Tense
Croak
Doppellusion
Magic Stone [Holy Type]
Spend MP to fill with mana and release healing light
Shadow Stomp
Flail
Dice Thrust [Common Skill]
A thrusting skill
Rolls a six-sided die and grants an
additional effect based on the rolled result
Total Multiplier x1.95
Ironpiercer 15% penetration
Critical 50% Penetration
Attack x1.95
Defense Penetration 65%
Flail
Dazzling Raana Decorative Blade
Attack: +12
Market Price: 17,000,000G
A glittering Raana short sword
A hunk of high-purity Raana Gold
Translator:
Sho Stifler
Timer:
Krzysztof Kunc
Editor:
Salem Alabanza
Quality Control:
Gabriella Alabanza
Final Quality Control:
Sriram Gurunathan